"Journey With You"
(Episode 7)
It's said that Jiangnan
produces beautiful women.
In my opinion,
although these beauties
all have some charm,
compared with Concubine Chen,
they all pale in comparison.
If Concubine Chen were still here,
the harem would surely
be much more splendid.
Your Majesty hasn't been
to Jiangnan for many years.
Visiting this place again
after Concubine Chen's passing,
it's inevitable to be reminded of her.
In my opinion,
even Concubine Chen's
spirit in heaven wouldn't want
to see Your Majesty so grieved for her.
The Empress is absolutely right.
After all, Concubine Chen left me
Qi'er and Heshu, such wonderful children.
Now Qi'er has grown up a lot.
It's time for him to stand on his own.
Father,
I have another request to make.
Yanzhi used to
serve in Mother's Yonghe Palace.
Mother took him in.
Now that Mother is gone,
I'd like to relieve him
of his duty to guard the imperial city
and give him an idle position.
You've always had a good relationship
with that hostage.
Why do you want to
relieve him of his duties now?
The royal brother is joking.
I think.
Pei Yanzhi is, after all, a
hostage from a foreign land.
We still need to distinguish
between closeness and distance.
I'm very pleased that
Qi'er has such thoughts.
I'm truly gratified.
Zhou'er,
don't make fun of your younger brother.
Father,
I was just joking around.
Don't take it seriously.
Your Majesty has
been showing great favor
to Qi'er and Heshu lately.
If Concubine Chen were to see this,
she would surely be
overwhelmed with surprise.
Alright,
let's not talk about her anymore.
Empress,
you're also my confidante.
Over the years,
you've worked hard managing the harem.
I've beared witness to it all.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I've just
done what I should do.
I've noticed lately that Zhou'er has
been busy with government affairs
and has lost a lot of weight.
Your Majesty,
why not assign some of the
government affairs to Qi'er?
Father, drink slowly.
I asked the landlady of Yanbo Tower
to prepare some Jinlingchun for you.
I'll go fetch it.
Heshu understands me the best.
Go quickly, go quickly.
Father,
don't be fooled by Heshu.
I think she
just wants to drink herself.
Why are you here?
Why can't I come?
There's no place in Jiangnan City
that this young lady can't go to.
Tell your royal brother and Brother Yanzhi
that we've prepared a great gift for them.
After your family banquet is over,
come with me to see it.
What gift?
Can you tell me now?
Of course not.
Anyway, it's a big catch.
So mysterious.
This princess doesn't even care.
You're just being stubborn.
Qi'er can help relieve my worries,
and Heshu can please me.
This trip to Jiangnan
has been truly enjoyable.
Father is really praising me too highly.
Compared with my royal brother,
I still have a long way to go.
Aunt Lin asked me to tell you
that she's prepared a great gift
for you and Brother Yanzhi.
But she didn't tell me what it is.
Royal brother,
In my opinion,
Father trusts you very much now.
Why not just tell Father about Yin Zhou's
planned rebellion and let him deal with it?
There's no evidence for this matter.
If we say it rashly,
Father will definitely
think I'm deliberately
sowing discord between
him and the royal brother.
That makes sense.
Fifth brother is being too modest.
On this trip to Jiangnan,
I've heard several times
from the accompanying officials say that...
What did they say?
I heard them say
that fifth brother has the same demeanor
as Father did in his youth,
resembling Father when he was young.
I've heard that
fifth brother has been getting close
to many ministers lately.
You must have learned a lot, right?
They really said that?
Father's heroic bearing
is naturally unparalleled.
I think those officials just said
some flattering words
which, when reaching the
royal elder brother's ears,
have changed their meaning.
Fifth brother,
I've also heard that you and that
hostage have an ambiguous relationship.
And now you've relieved him of his duties.
Are you really able to distinguish
between closeness and distance,
or are you afraid that people will find out
that you're colluding with him?
Royal brother really likes to joke.
Father, forgive me.
I've had too much to drink
and said something inappropriate on a whim.
Please punish me, Father.
Father,
I'm innocent.
I just want to stay by Father's side
and help relieve his worries.
I've never overstepped my bounds.
I hope Father can see this clearly.
Father,
Since royal brother came to Jiangnan,
he has been constantly thinking of Mother.
He's been going to places
where Mother used to go.
How could he possibly form factions
and seek private gains
as the royal elder brother said?
Please investigate clearly, Father.
This family banquet is boring.
Let me help Your Majesty go back
and have a good rest.
Surround Yin Qi's courtyard.
Wait for the prince's
order before taking action.
Yes.
Fifth Prince Yin Qi,
greedy for power,
conspired with Su He to rebel.
Upon hearing this,
I dispatched troops to rescue the emperor
and protect Father's safety.
To protect Father's safety.
Yin Qi resisted stubbornly.
I had no choice but to
shoot him dead on the spot.
Understand?
As for Pei Yanzhi...?
I want to see with my own eyes
his heartbroken expression
when he hears that Yin Qi is dead.
That look of utter despair.
Understood, Master.
Prince,
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Let's go to Father's bedroom quickly.
Help!
There are assassins!
Protect the emperor!
Deshun, Deshun!
What's going on?
Why are they making such a racket?
The imperial palace is heavily guarded.
How could assassins get in?
Who are you?
How dare you break into
the imperial palace at night?
We're following the
orders of the fifth prince
to come and take Yin Zhao's head.
Qi'er,
he's usually so well-behaved.
How could he possibly commit such a
treasonous and rebellious act?
You are all subjects of Daxing.
But you've been deceived by Yin Zhou.
If you turn back now,
I can spare your lives.
Stop talking nonsense.
Tonight is the night you
and the old emperor die.
Kill!
Something's not right.
Go report to the master.
Yes.
Go, hurry!
I don't want to just run away like this.
Princess,
do you know what you're saying?
Of course.
I'm the sixth princess.
At such an important moment,
why can I only run away?
If I can't help royal brother,
and if something happens to him,
how will I be able to
face others in the future?
At a time of life and death,
you're telling me this?
I know you're trying to stop me,
but I...
I...
Are you really sure?
What?
If you have this determination,
then this lady will
accompany you to the end.
Master, master, master!
The guards in the emperor's bedroom
were originally all killed.
But two teams of guards
suddenly appeared from nowhere.
And for some reason,
the archers didn't take their positions.
If we fight head-on,
we don't have a sure chance of winning.
The brothers sent me to report
and ask for your decision.
How's Yin Qi?
There aren't many guards in his courtyard.
We should be able to succeed quickly.
No matter how many
guards are in the bedroom,
they can't match our death squads.
Let the death squads I arranged
outside the imperial palace rush in.
The most important task tonight
is to kill Yin Qi and Father.
Understood, Master.
There are guards by Father's side
that I didn't know about.
Yin Qi,
It's him.
It must be him.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Now, the emperor firmly believes
that Yin Qi is planning a rebellion.
As long as Yin Qi is dead,
there will be no evidence left.
Then, Your Highness
will have all the power.
Those thieves have all retreated.
Are my reinforcements here?
Your Majesty,
let's go quickly.
If the barbarians rush in later,
we won't even have a chance to escape.
You...
From today on,
I finally don't have to be
controlled by others anymore,
and compromise for survival.
Yin Qi, Yin Qi,
you're the ultimate defeated opponent.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
Your wish
has been fulfilled.
This position
finally
belongs only to me.
Rebellious son!
Father!
You...
Royal brother,
you've lost.
It seems I've come
at the right time.
Father!
Come with me quickly!
Where are you taking me?
Father,
all of this
was done by your royal elder brother,
right?
Father,
You've guessed it.
This isn't the place to talk.
Come with me to see someone.
All truths will be revealed.
Don't move, don't move.
Fengsun,
You've conspired with
the Central Plains people,
betrayed your kin.
Aren't you afraid of divine punishment?
Why are you asking me, Uncle?
Uncle should know better than anyone
that I want to
slice you into a thousand pieces.
Fengsun,
I've treated you well.
I've even raised Aruna as if
she were my own daughter.
And yet you betrayed me!
Bullshit!
You took advantage of Harchagai's death,
kidnapped the princess,
and forced the master to come to
the Central Plains as a hostage.
With your long-standing
ambition for the Khan's throne,
if the gods have eyes,
you'll be the first to be punished.
I warned you, Uncle,
not to get involved in the succession
struggle in the Central Plains.
But you, Uncle,
just wouldn't listen to me.
Uncle,
Reaching this point today,
you can only blame yourself.
Su He,
You...
Your Majesty,
For so many years,
I've been sending messages to Su He
just to gain his trust.
I just didn't expect that
the Crown Prince would
exploit Su He's ambition
and try to ally with him
to usurp the throne.
Yin Zhao,
You've won by luck this time,
not because you're capable.
It's because you're lucky.
If you were born in the Talhan tribe,
I'm afraid
you wouldn't even qualify to fight me.
The winner becomes king,
the loser becomes a bandit.
Do whatever you want with me,
I'm at your mercy.
Father,
I was able to find out in time
that the royal brother was
conspiring with Su He to rebel
all thanks to Yan Zhi's
enduring humiliation for years,
making Su He think
that Yan Zhi was his spy planted in Daxing.
This is how their ambitions
and claws were revealed.
This rebellious son!
Where is he now?
I won't spare him lightly!
Speak!
What's the signal you
agreed upon with Yin Zhou?
You can kill me, but I won't say.
Good.
Then I'll grant you your wish.
Stop!
It seems Uncle has also learned
that a wise man knows
when to submit in the Central Plains.
Speak quickly!
We had an agreement.
After the deed is done,
I'll order someone to
set off two smoke bombs.
Haven't I treated you and
the queen well enough?
You dare to conspire with outsiders
and attempt to kill
your father and brother,
and usurp the throne?
You're truly a rebellious son!
I've spoiled you too much,
making you arrogant and complacent.
How dare you covet my throne!
Father,
You ask me why I rebelled?
Don't you know?
You're the one who started all this!
Father,
You...
What nonsense are you talking?
You've played political games,
deliberately pitting my
brothers against each other.
You watched us from on high,
fighting and grabbing.
Making me think I could
become the crown prince.
In the end,
I was just a pawn
in your political games.
How comfortably
do you sit on this dragon throne?
Nonsense!
Who taught you to say this?
Was it the queen?
Come here!
Bring the queen here!
I'll interrogate her in person.
Mother!
Mother knows nothing about this.
Mother is just a woman in the palace.
She sees all the concubines around you,
and as the queen, she can't be jealous.
She vents all her anger
on me.
Have you ever
cared about me, your
son, even for a moment?
How dare you!
The glory of your maternal family
was all given by me.
Even your ability to resist me
was given by me.
What more do you want?
Royal brother,
now that things have come to this,
are you still obsessed?
You keep saying
that everything today was forced upon you,
but the one who covets power
is you.
If it weren't for your greed for power,
you wouldn't have failed today.
What do you know?
You've had your mother's
love since you were a child,
and Father's favoritism.
Even
such a loyal dog.
You...
Do you know
what I've been through these years?
Royal brother,
Stop this.
Father will spare your life.
Yin Qi,
I've failed today,
I've been defeated by myself.
You, born of a lowly woman,
how dare you lecture me?
Yin Qi,
I did think about
sparing your life.
But you kept taking what
belonged to me over and over.
Even the little bit of love
and trust from Father,
you wanted to take away.
Why?
Why you all,
why won't you all leave me alone?
All of this started because of you.
Since that's the case,
even though I've failed,
I,
will make you accompany me in death.
Why?
Why did you stop me?
If Your Highness admits
your mistake to the emperor,
His Majesty will surely spare your life.
But
if you kill Yin Qi,
you'll really
have no way back.
No!
Don't go!
Don't leave me!
Please!
If even you leave me,
I'll really have nothing left.
Your Highness,
don't cry.
Your Highness
is the best person
in this world.
Live well,
live on.
If there's an afterlife...
I still want to be
the prince's
sharp blade.
Zhou'er.
You.
Only now do I understand
that long ago,
the idealistic
and ambitious Yin Zhou
was already killed
by my father and mother.
Today,
the only person in the world
who truly loved me
has also left me.
You think you've won?
No,
there are never any winners.
You,
will end up like me,
living forever in an endless hell,
watching helplessly as
you lose everything.
Today,
it is I
who am freed.
Zhou'er.
Father.
Father Emperor!
Zhou'er.
Yan Zhi.
We've really done it.
This time around,
we're both still alive.
A Qi,
it was you who did it.
You changed our fates,
and even
the fate of the Daxing Empire.
But.
I can't bring myself to be happy.
Seeing what happened to the
Crown Prince and Wei Ziming,
I don't feel like I've won.
The Crown Prince was right.
In this treacherous imperial city,
there are never any winners.
A Qi,
don't think like that.
If Yin Zhou had really
ascended to the throne,
and gained control of the world,
what kind of life
would the people of Daxing have had?
You're right.
In my previous life,
I spent three years at the border,
seeing too much suffering among the people.
It really opened my eyes.
What are you doing here?
Brother,
the carriage is ready.
You two,
is there something
I don't know about?
Good sister,
let's go, let's go.
Tang'er,
On the day we parted ways,
I always felt we would meet again.
I never expected that
after all these years,
we would truly
never meet again in this life.
Aunt,
don't be too sad.
I'm sure Aunt Tang missed you terribly
while she was alive.
Even though you haven't
seen each other for years,
your hearts have always been connected.
That's better than being together every day
yet lacking any understanding.
Sister Xianyue is absolutely right.
Mother would think the same way.
Aunt Lin,
after we return to the capital,
I'll have to trouble you
to take care of Mother.
Of course.
By the way,
when are you leaving?
We're leaving tomorrow.
After the Crown Prince passed away,
Father Emperor seems to
have aged ten years overnight.
It's better to return to the capital early.
You'll face many more challenges
when you return to the capital,
but I believe
that no matter what,
as long as you stand together,
you'll overcome any obstacle.
This matter is definitely
related to Talhan.
As a hostage,
I must give Daxing an explanation.
Yan Zhi,
you're being too formal.
Don't worry,
I'll plead with King Father on your behalf.
Xianyue,
let's go back.
This one,
not this one.
Wrap up all the rest for me.
My lucky star,
you have excellent taste!
You don't need to buy so much.
The capital has everything.
Besides, I'm a princess.
These are all specialties from Jiangnan.
Besides,
what your father buys for you
and what I buy for you
are not the same.
Here you go.
Let's go to the rouge shop up ahead.
You're practically
shouting from the rooftops
that you're the richest man in Jiangnan.
You don't have to be so polite.
Buying rouge?
Top-quality rouge.
You won't miss me when I leave, will you?
Don't flatter yourself.
I was thinking that since
you can't often leave the palace,
I should buy you
plenty to last you a while.
In case you secretly cry yourself to sleep.
Selling rouge!
Aunt Lin,
we'll take our leave now.
We'll reunite after
you return to the capital.
Good children,
take care on your journey.
I've already arranged
for people to escort you.
Heshu,
we should go.
Aunt Lin,
I'll take my leave.
Yanzhi,
Are you really going back to Talhan?
After all these years,
Su He has turned Talhan
into a mess.
I think
it's even worse than what
you saw on the border in your past life.
I must go back to Talhan
to help my elder brother revive it
and let my people
live a peaceful and prosperous life.
I understand what you're saying,
I just can't bear to part with you.
Why don't I go back with you?
I'm very familiar with Talhan.
The lamb in Talhan is the best.
You...
But now, as the only
adult prince of the Daxing Dynasty,
you have heavy responsibilities.
Don't talk nonsense.
I understand what you're saying.
But with your abilities,
in no more than three years,
Talhan will surely become
what you envision it to be.
If you need anything,
I will do my utmost.
What's wrong?
Maybe I caught a cold.
The journey has been tiring.
Fifth Prince,
Young Master,
His Majesty wants you to go to
the imperial study for a discussion.
Qi'er,
You've rendered meritorious service
in protecting me this time.
What reward do you want?
Just tell me.
I will surely grant it to you.
This is just my duty.
I dare not take credit for it.
You can put righteousness above family ties
and know what's important.
It seems that Concubine
Chen’s teachings have paid off.
Go ahead,
what reward do you want?
Your Majesty,
I've been in Daxing for ten years now.
During these ten years,
I've been constantly
missing the grasslands of my hometown.
I earnestly request Your
Majesty's permission
to let me return to Talhan.
After I return to Talhan,
I will surely govern the tribe well
and obey Your Majesty's commands,
never again letting border disturbances
become a problem for both countries.
Aunt,
I'll finish going through
these accounts soon.
The little boss is so diligent.
It seems she doesn't miss me at all.
Why are you back?
My elder brother said we did a good deed
by protecting His Majesty.
He went to plead with Father Emperor
to allow me to stay in Jiangnan.
We did a good deed?
Let's go.